Tushar Rathod

917600464414

rathodtushar55055@gmail.com

Surat, Gujrat, India

Rathodtushar.carrd.co

in/tushar-rathod-5a1964149

Profile summary

Dedicated Shopify full stack developer having 5+ years of experience.

Managed a lot of the projects during the job as an employee and also as a project manager.

I have the best project management skill in Shopify store development and App development.

I can utilize my expertise in technical skills, towards the development and implementation of the new ideas, contributing to growth of the organization.

Core PHP is the first step in my developing a career and I am an expert in core PHP, Ajax, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Shopify Liquid, Polaris, and Shopify API.

Skills

Shopify App

Shopify Theme

PHP

HTML

JQuery

CSS

WordPress

SQL

BE in computer engineering

2014-2017

I have done my bachelor in computer engineering from the government engineering college Dahod.

Education

Diploma in computer engineering

2011-2014

Diploma in computer engineering done from government polytechnic Bhuj

SSC

2010 - 2011

Experience

 Shopify Developer - Codelock Solutions 2021 - Present

Worked as a project manager and I were handling a team of Shopify developers and I am able to handle the most complex functionality in Shopify.

• Shopify Developer - Identixweb Pvt Ltd 2018 - 2020

I started my career in Shopify from Identixweb and I have done many Shopify public and private apps during my job period in Identixweb.

• PHP Developer - Identixweb Pvt Ltd 2017 - 2018

PHP is my first skill which I got from Identixweb and I have built many Shopify apps in the PHP language.